var Quiz = '{"Question1": [{"Question" : "Central obesity, also known as android obesity, is the increased accumulation of adipose tissue in which of the following areas?","1":"Thorax, abdomen, subcutaneous tissue","2":"Thorax, abdomen, internal organs","3":"Abdomen, hips, thighs","4":"Hips, limbs, subcutaneous tissue","Answer" : 2}],"Question2": [{"Question" : "In obesity, the compliance of the lungs is reduced due to deposition of fat within the mediastinum. Outward movement of the chest wall and downward movement of the diaphragm are similarly impacted. Which of the following statements hold true?","1":"Resting volume of the lung remains unchanged","2":"Expiratory reserve volume is increased","3":"Functional residual capacity is substantially reduced","4":"Tidal volume is increased","Answer" : 3}],"Question3": [{"Question" : "Which of the following is the most common cause of pulmonary congestion in obese patients?","1":"Pulmonary embolism","2":"Increased blood volume with diminished left ventricular compliance","3":"Left ventricular heart failure","4":"Pulmonary hypertension","Answer" : 2}],"Question4": [{"Question" : "The heart has three different fat depots: epicardial, pericardial and intracellular. Epicardial fat is located on the surface of the heart. It covers 80% of the heart’s surface (coverage can range from 60% to 100%). Among the areas it is present in, which area normally has the greatest amount of adipose tissue?","1":"Base of the heart","2":"Atrioventricular groove","3":"Apex of the heart","4":"Lateral right ventricular wall","Answer" : 4}],"Question5": [{"Question" : "Obesity in young children can lead to changes in heart anatomy. The heart adapts to the extra work demands from obesity. Cardiac remodelling becomes significant at a BMI of 19 in 10-year-olds (equivalent to BMI of 25 in adults, which is the overweight threshold). Which of the following statements are true?","1":"Left ventricular cross-section becomes rounder","2":"Septal wall thickness increases","3":"Heart is tilted away from normal vertical axis","4":"All of the above","Answer" : 5}],"Question6": [{"Question" : "Which of the following is least likely to be reversible in obese patients who have lost weight?","1":"Increased central blood volume","2":"Lung compliance","3":"High cardiac output","4":"Left ventricular hypertrophy","Answer" : 4}],"Question7": [{"Question" : "Which part of the heart can you feel pulsing if you put your hand on the chest wall at the left fifth intercostal space, midclavicular line?","1":"Aortic arch","2":"Left atrium","3":"Apex","4":"Mitral valve","Answer" : 3}],"Question8": [{"Question" : "Which part of the heart is directly behind the sternum?","1":"Right ventricle","2":"Left ventricle","3":"Right atrium","4":"Anterior margin of left atrium","Answer" : 1}],"Question9": [{"Question" : "Which part of the myocardium will most likely be affected if the circumflex branch of the left coronary artery is occluded?","1":"Anterior ⅓ of interventricular septum","2":"Posterior ⅔ of interventricular septum","3":"Lateral wall of left ventricle","4":"Base of heart","Answer" : 3}],"Question10": [{"Question" : "A 54-year-old woman is in the hospital with complaints of leg swelling. Physical examination confirms edema, and further investigation with ultrasound reveals a faulty tricuspid valve. Which area in the heart will blood regurgitate into?","1":"Left atrium","2":"Ascending aorta","3":"Right atrium","4":"Pulmonary trunk","Answer" : 3}]}'